mutantbox.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy

The effective date of this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") is July 31st, 2015.

**1\. Introduction**

Mutant Box Limited and its subsidiaries, including but not limited to Mutant Box Interactive Limited (collectively, "Mutantbox” or “we”, or "us”) respect the privacy of its online visitors and users of its products and services. Mutantbox recognizes the importance of protecting information collected from users and has adopted this privacy policy to inform users about how Mutantbox gathers, stores, and uses information derived from their use of Mutantbox products, services and online sites. 

This policy is current as of its last revision date. However, please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy.

**2\. What Information Is Collected**

Personal information: Mutantbox’s primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the Service and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the Service.

When you install any of the Mutantbox games or applications, we may collect and record the information you provide us voluntarily through the social networking website in accordance with their policies and terms.

The types of personal information collected in accordance with the activities listed above may vary depending on the activity. Personal information may include:

i. Your name;

ii. User identification number;

iii. Email address;

iv. Home address;

v. Phone number.

vi. Instant message account

Non-personal information is information that is not, on its own, personal information, such as your IP address, but that may be considered part of an individual's personal information if combined with other identifiers in a way that enables identification of an individual.

Additionally, we may acquire information from you through:

i.Your access and participation in message boards on the Service;

ii.Your email of a question to our customer support;

iii.Your purchase of a virtual product of any type.

When you play a Mutantbox game, on Mutantbox's website at www.mutantbox.com (the "Site") or on your social network page or on someone else's page or through your mobile device, we may record information regarding the use of that game, and we may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that page.

The Service will also record game play information such as your high scores or game session duration. When you invite new members into your network or send messages through Mutantbox's applications, we collect and maintain the information associated with those messages, including email address and content.

Financial information: When you pay for products offered for purchase though the Service, we will also collect your billing address and complete credit card information that enables us to receive your payment. Our payment processing service provider may also retain this information to enable you to purchase additional items through our Service without having to re-enter it each time. We do not directly access, store or collect your credit card information and we will not use your payment information we collect except as needed to fulfill your purchase and/or communicate with you regarding your transaction.

Mutantbox will never at any time ask you for your credit card or bank account information, your login or password, or national identification numbers via any unsolicited means, including email and telephone calls.

Third Party Cookies: We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the site. These companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites and your interaction with our products and services in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. However, no personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address or telephone number) will be connected with such information. They may use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services and may be used to keep track of user response to each advertisement. These targeted advertisements may appear on the site or on other sites that you visit. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag or cookies, which are industry standard technologies used by most major websites. If you do not want such companies to collect this information you may opt-out.

Web Beacons: The Websites may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or a "web beacon") that allow a website to track the effectiveness of marketing campaigns. No personally identifiable information will be transmitted via web beacons.

**3\. What We Do With Your Personal Information**

Mutantbox uses your Personal Information to operate, for the improvement of the Services, and to assist you. We assign every player a User ID that contains no Personal Information, which is shared with the Third Party relevant to the Services.

We use your Personal Information, and Log File Information related to you, in a variety of ways including, but not limited to, customer service, account management, enforcement of our Terms of Service, marketing, promotions, and site improvement. We may also use your Personal Information to prevent cheating, crime, or fraud. We may also need to pass your Personal Information to fraud prevention agencies and other organizations involved in crime and fraud prevention and as otherwise required by applicable law. Additionally, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy of Mutantbox, or other similar events, customer information may be transferred to Mutantbox' successor or assignee, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law. 

**4\. Information Sharing With Third Parties**

We partner with Third Parties to obtain marketing feedback, process payments, analyze metrics, and improve our systems. We will not share your Personal Information with Third Parties unless express consent is given by you. The purpose of our sharing your information with Third Parties is to provide a better service to you and we take necessary measures to protect your identity when dealing with Third Parties.

Mutantbox is not liable for losses or damages resulting from or associated with the Privacy Policy of any Third Party. We ask all of our players to carefully read the relevant Third Party's Privacy Policy to stay informed and protected.

**5\. Security of Your Personal Information**

Personally identifiable information is used internally by Mutantbox to deliver, develop and improve products, content and services, to which users have subscribed, and to answer users’ requests. In addition, Mutantbox may allow third parties performing services under contract with Mutantbox, such as order or payment processors or merchandise warehouse and fulfillment services, to access and use personally identifiable information, but only to the extent necessary to provide those services. 

Mutantbox may use personally identifiable information provided by users to send them information about Mutantbox, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials, but only if the users agree to receive such communications. Mutantbox will not share any personally identifiable information with third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

When you create an account in Mutantbox online websites, we collects a user's email address and username, and at the user's option, first and last name. Depending on their settings, users agree that some of this information may be searchable and available to other users within Mutantbox. We has no obligation to keep private personally identifiable information that a user makes available to other users via Mutantbox online websites or other Mutantbox software, such as in multiplayer chat or other public functions. 

External websites and companies with links to and from Mutantbox's online sites and products may collect personally identifiable information about users when users visit their websites. Third party publishers may also collect personally identifiable information as a requirement of accessing their games or content. Mutantbox's privacy policy does not extend to those websites and companies or third party publishers with links to or from Mutantbox's products and online websites or who collect personally identifiable information through their game available on Mutantbox online websites. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies.

Mutantbox may release personally identifiable information to comply with court orders or laws that require us to disclose such information. In the event of a reorganization, sale or merger we may transfer personally identifiable information to the relevant third party with the user’s consent if required by law.

**6\. Policy Recarding Children Under the Age of 13**

Mutantbox does not knowingly collect nor solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allows such persons to access our Service. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Site or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents or guardians for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

**7\. Cookies and Other Information on a User's Machine**

Mutantbox’s products, services and sites may employ cookies and other technologies such as web beacons and pixel tags. Cookies are bits of electronic information that can be transferred to a user's hard drive to customize a person's use of a product or online site, keep records of a user's access to an online site or product, or store information needed by the user on a regular basis. Use of cookies is typically associated with websites. For example, when you sign in to Mutantbox online websites , we stores your user id and a combination of your IP address and time of login as a cookie on your hard drive. This cookie allows you to move from page to page without having to sign in again on each page. Similarly, if you enter information during your session, such as age verification data, this will be stored as a cookie and you will not have to re-enter such information during that session. We may also use third party web site analytic tools that employ cookies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information concerning use of our websites, such as referring web site addresses, page views and browser types.

However, users can disable cookies by changing their browser settings. Mutantbox also stores on a user’s hard drive a unique authorization key or CD-Key that is either entered by the user or downloaded automatically during product registration. This authorization key is used to identify a user as valid and allow access to Mutantbox's products, services and third party games. This key is necessary for Mutantbox to supply any products and services subscribed by users.

Information regarding Mutantbox billing, a user’s Mutantbox account, a user's Internet connection and the Mutantbox software installed on a user's computer is uploaded to the server in connection with the user's use of Steam and Mutantbox software. Mutantbox software automatically generates and submits to Mutantbox bug reports upon a crash or other fault in the Mutantbox software, services or Steam games. This automatically generated bug report information may include information about other software or hardware on a user's system. Mutantbox does not associate and store the automatically generated bug report information with users’ personally identifiable information. Any bug reporting information manually submitted by users (e.g. through Mutantbox's Bug Reporter form) is associated and stored with personally identifiable information sent voluntarily by the user through a bug report.

**8\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

Mutantbox may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use personal information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Service or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Service after such changes have been first posted. If you object to any change, your sole recourse shall be to immediately terminate your account and cease using the Site and Service.

**9\. Contact Us**

The Policy and your use of the Services shall be governed by and construed and take effect in accordance with the laws of Hong Kong. With respect to any questions, disputes, suits, action or proceedings arising out of or in connection with the Policy, you irrevocably submit to  the Hong Kong International Arbitration Center. If you have any questions about the Policy, or the practices mentioned within, please send an email to support@mutantbox.com.
